<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<html 

	width="600"
	height="400"
	
	scrollbarColor1="0x333333"
	scrollbarColor2="0xDFDFDF"

>

	<title><![CDATA[A Little Bit About Whats Going On At Our School]]></title>
	<text><![CDATA[<img src="thumbnail.png" width="250" height="150"><font>A guide is for all high school students who are committed to making their schools, their communities and the world a better place. It’s intended for you if you’re willing to help a friend or stranger in trouble. It’s for you if you believe you can help improve and save lives.
We are in partnership with The American Red Cross and more closely in tune with the local Red Cross GHAC.
In addition we give our support to Houston Children's Charity.
We also support “Sponsor a Child” group where we donate a monthly allowance from the student body and send it to main group where they provide for a larger cause.
The club also partakes in organizing a blood drive in association with the Red Cross and its staff.
We also require our club members to do some sort of volunteering and each member must collect 12 hours by the end of the year. These have to be done during the school year and up to 10 hours in total can be transferred from other clubs such as NHS. This club is an outreach club and for us to do that we must stretch ourselves a little bit so that the community can benefit. Nobody is forcing you to join, it is a self-motivated action to better serve the community.
One group volunteering event has to be completed by each member. This allows the student to collaborate and volunteer and have fun while doing so. Every month Naman and I will be offering such events at a unique location. We will configure the schedule once the total number of members is confirmed.
An award will be given to the most hardworking member. No officers are allowed to participate. Voting will be held late April. Winner will be announced in May.
We also inform our students of safety in CPR, diseases, lifeguard, and fire safety.
There will be a website maintained by an officer where updates will be posted. A username and password will be given to all members who can login to see their tasks and information. This is going to be a trial and error since the website will be removed if not successful. Information will be sent out through Facebook as well.</font>]]></text>
	
</html>