<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Jobs>

	<settings>
		
		<text>resume.php</text>
		
		<upload></upload>
		
	</settings>
		
	<content title="Careers" urlTitle="Careers" url="/careers">	
	
		

		<item title="Prepress Specialist"  date="Paris, France" urlTitle="Prepress Specialist" url="/prepress-specialist-1/" id="1"  mainTitle="Job Opening Details" uploadTitle="Upload your resume" contactTitle="Job Application">
			<small_description><![CDATA[ The Prepress Specialist’s role is to provide prepress expertise, knowledge and support to the Creative and Production teams in Plano for the client. The Prepress Specialist also supports and works with the prepress team in St. Louis to build prepress ready files for the end print process. Some of the responsibilities include applying master dies, checking colors, bleeds and trims, gathering fonts, placing hi-res images and adding necessary traps for the print process. The Prepress Specialist works closely with the project management staff to support the clients overall needs from a prepress standpoint. ]]></small_description>

			<big_description><![CDATA[ <p>Position Overview<br />
<br />
The Prepress Specialist’s role is to provide prepress expertise, knowledge and support to the Creative and Production teams in Plano for the client.  The Prepress Specialist also supports and works with the prepress team in St. Louis to build prepress ready files for the end print process.  Some of the responsibilities include applying master dies, checking colors, bleeds and trims, gathering fonts, placing hi-res images and adding necessary traps for the print process.  The Prepress Specialist works closely with the project management staff to support the clients overall needs from a prepress standpoint.<br />
<br />
Essential Job Functions</p>
<ul>
    <li>Interpret and apply relevant information obtained from job tickets and assess when additional information is needed</li>
    <li>Build constructive relationships with team members and production personnel</li>
    <li>Prepare files for output to film/plate</li>
    <li>Layout/impose files on printer templates</li>
    <li>Set up register targets and trim lines for production</li>
    <li>Set line screens, resolution, and other press-specific settings</li>
    <li>Prepare layouts by placing art and text; specify bleeds, clear zones and coverages; complete color separations; color correcting and resizing photographs; revise and modify existing files</li>
    <li>Maintain quality results by proofing and pre-flighting layouts, including required files, fonts, links, and call-outs; confirm design printability, including traps, overprints, and minimum half-tone dots and line weights</li>
    <li>Maintain consistent appearance and standards across projects</li>
    <li>Accomplish organization goals by accepting ownership for new and different requests; explore opportunities to add value to job accomplishments</li>
</ul>
<p>Basic Job Qualifications: Skills and Abilities</p>
<ul>
    <li>Strong understanding of flexo printing methods and processes</li>
    <li>Ability to solve problems when working independently</li>
    <li>Ability to meet tight deadlines and work well under pressure</li>
    <li>Organized and detail-oriented</li>
    <li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li>
    <li>Work well independently and in a team environment with a positive attitude</li>
    <li>Must be able to multi-task within a fast-paced working environment</li>
</ul>
<p>Education/Experience/Training</p>
<ul>
    <li>5+ years experience in a fast paced packaging prepress department</li>
    <li>MAC Proficient with working experience of Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign</li>
    <li>Advanced knowledge of Macintosh and Windows platforms and operating systems</li>
    <li>Knowledge of printing terminology and practices</li>
    <li>General knowledge of utility programs such as file compression, disk repair, print spoolers, PC to Mac, and Mac to PC conversion processes</li>
    <li>Experience with an automated digital prepress workflow system</li>
    <li>Must understand 4 – 8 color printing techniques, trapping and spot color separations</li>
    <li>Working knowledge of flexo, gravure and offset package printing</li>
</ul>
<p>Working Conditions &amp; Physical Demands (Walking, lifting, equipment, operation, etc.)</p>
<ul>
    <li>Normal office environment</li>
</ul> ]]></big_description>
		</item>


		<item title="Project Manager, Digital Solutions"  date="New York" urlTitle="" url="/project-manager--digital-solutions-2/" id="2" mainTitle="Random text goes here..." contactTitle="Details about">
			<small_description><![CDATA[ Essential Job Functions<br />
    * Responsible for ensuring customer satisfaction<br />
    * Work with client base to understand expectations/needs<br />
    * Execute project plans, timelines, and technical specifications inclusive of use-cases<br />
    * Provide client training and system documentation upon project completion<br />
    * Client presentations<br />
    * Perform other duties as required ]]></small_description>
			<big_description><![CDATA[ <p>Essential Job Functions</p>
<ul>
    <li>Responsible for ensuring customer satisfaction</li>
    <li>Work with client base to understand expectations/needs</li>
    <li>Execute project plans, timelines, and technical specifications inclusive of use-cases</li>
    <li>Provide client training and system documentation upon project completion</li>
    <li>Client presentations</li>
    <li>Perform other duties as required</li>
</ul>
<p>Basic Job Qualifications: Skills and Abilities</p>
<ul>
    <li>Strong project management and presentation skills</li>
    <li>Very strong written and verbal communication skills</li>
    <li>Creative thinker</li>
    <li>Ability to work in a team environment</li>
    <li>Organization and cleanliness of workspace</li>
    <li>Ability to build and maintain long-term customer relationships</li>
    <li>Maintain a professional demeanor with coworkers</li>
</ul>
<p>Education/Experience/Training</p>
<ul>
    <li>BS of Computer Science degree or 4+ years of Industry related experience; specialized in Packaging/Prepress Graphics</li>
</ul>
<p>Working Conditions &amp; Physical Demands (Walking, lifting, equipment, operation, etc.)</p>
<ul>
    <li>Normal office environment</li>
    <li>Travel as required</li>
</ul> ]]></big_description>
		</item>


		<item title="Creative Director"  date="Canada" urlTitle="Creative Director" url="/creative-director-3/" id="3" mainTitle="Some Details" contactTitle="Enquiry about">

			<small_description><![CDATA[ The Creative Director (Packaging) is responsible for the ultimate strategic intent, visual appeal and communicative success of each assigned project. He or she leads a designer/writer team to complete projects, offering guidance and mentoring them through the process. The CD leads concept development and brainstorming sessions, oversees strategic direction, provides and critiques visual and copy solutions, and presents the rationale for their choices effectively. These key leaders inspire and motivate others to help them reach their creative potential. They direct the projects to ensure that they are completed accurately, on time and within budgetary constraints. The CD may either be an active designer or copywriter with marketing savvy. Regardless of his or her specialty, the CD must know how to judge and marry the visual and copy properly for impactful communication.  ]]></small_description>
			<big_description><![CDATA[ <p>The Creative Director (Packaging) is responsible for the ultimate strategic intent, visual appeal and communicative success of each assigned project. He or she leads a designer/writer team to complete projects, offering guidance and mentoring them through the process. The CD leads concept development and brainstorming sessions, oversees strategic direction, provides and critiques visual and copy solutions, and presents the rationale for their choices effectively. These key leaders inspire and motivate others to help them reach their creative potential. They direct the projects to ensure that they are completed accurately, on time and within budgetary constraints. The CD may either be an active designer or copywriter with marketing savvy. Regardless of his or her specialty, the CD must know how to judge and marry the visual and copy properly for impactful communication.</p>
<ul>
    <li>The CD must be well-versed in the principles of design, and have a working knowledge of illustration, photography, icons, typography and color theory.</li>
    <li>The CD is responsible for bringing big ideas and distinctive creative solutions to the table, with an understanding of the brand, its marketing strategies, and the Clients’ industry. The CD must lead the team in conceptual and strategic development, and train and guide the ADs and CWs to develop their abilities to do so as well. This includes not only ideation, but the ability to express the idea and present it in a variety of formats, both internally (to the ECD and Account Services team) and to Clients., with clear rationale behind his or her decisions.</li>
    <li>As well as doing design or writing work of their own, the CD provides guidance and critique of AD/ Designers’ work, and offers opinions, suggestions and insights to co-workers. The CD also mentors the CWs and encourages fresh writing style that meets the marketing objectives and enhances the design message. The goal of the CD should be to nurture the creative team members to help them reach their potential and overcome their individual weaknesses.</li>
    <li>The CD is expected to be flexible in style and encourage diversity in style, to be accurate to specifications, true to deadlines under pressure, helpful in attitude, and resilient in the face of ever-changing Client demands.</li>
    <li>The CD works closely with the Project Manager and Account Director to help our Clients succeed. This involves proper planning in regard to providing estimates for creative time and clear communication when those boundaries are being pushed.</li>
    <li>As a member of the Creative Leadership Team, the CD is expected to project a positive attitude and show enthusiasm for projects large and small.</li>
    <li>The CD is expected to stay on top of creative software, current design trends and the influences of popular culture.</li>
</ul>
<p>Requirements:</p>
<ul>
    <li>This position usually requires a Bachelor’s Degree in design art, marketing or a related field, or equivalent with a minimum of 10 years of experience in the field.</li>
    <li>Knowledge of layout principles, aesthetic design concepts, branding, typography and color theory essential</li>
    <li>CD/D: Proficient in current CS2 Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Quark X-press, In-Design CD/CW: Should have some skills in above software and Microsoft Office</li>
    <li>An understanding of new media, animation, sound, text and video is a plus</li>
</ul>
<p>Reports to: Executive Creative Director</p> ]]></big_description>
		</item>


	</content>

</Jobs>
