<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<content Name="FEATURES">
    <item Border="10" Width="600" Height="360" ><![CDATA[<img src="content/feature1.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Accordion Navigation</b></font><br>To add content pages you can edit the navigation XML file where you can specify each content page to be loaded. The main navigation also supports Sub Menus, see "Sub Menu Example" in the menu. There are also settings in the XML to change the image path to Company Logo, edit footer text and show/hide the navigation menu on start up.<br><br><img src="content/feature2.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Dynamic Backgrounds</b></font><br>You can easily add your own backgrounds by saving them to a specific folder and adding each JPEG path in an XML file. Single or multiple backgrounds can be loaded. You can also define the delay in seconds between each background in the backgrounds XML file.<br><br><br><img src="content/feature3.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Slideshow Component</b></font><br>With the Slideshow Component you can add multiple images and add content text in the slideshow XML file. You can also set the delay in seconds between each slides and set the URL link when each slide image is pressed.<br><br><br><img src="content/feature4.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Team Members Component</b></font><br>With the Team Members Component you can add your company staff members bio's by saving their photo to a specific folder and adding their details in the Team Members XML file. The copy supports HTML formatting so you can change font size, colour and decoration and add hyper links. Multiple categories are also supported.<br><br><img src="content/feature5.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Dynamic Content Window</b></font><br>With this component you can create multiple content windows like this one. By editing each content window XML file you can specify the window dimensions and border size. The copy supports HTML formatting so you can change font size, colour and decoration and add hyper links and images.<br><br><img src="content/feature6.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>News Component</b></font><br>With the News Component you can add news articles by editing the News XML file and saving images to specific folders. The copy supports HTML formatting so you can change font size, colour and decoration and add hyper links.<br><br><br><img src="content/feature7.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Video Gallery Component</b></font><br>You can add videos in either FLV or MP4 format, paths and titles defined in the XML. For the thumbnails you can specify the number of rows, columns and the number of thumbnails to appear on screen. Multiple galleries are also supported and the video player supports full screen video mode.<br><br><img src="content/feature8.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>Image Gallery Component</b></font><br>With the Image gallery Component you can add images by editing the Image Gallery XML file and saving the images to specific folders. The copy supports HTML formatting so you can change font size, colour and decoration and add hyper links. Multiple galleries are also supported.<br><br><img src="content/feature9.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>PHP Contact Form Component</b></font><br>Users can send mails directly from this template to your mailbox. All you need to do is define your email address. The contact details can be change by editing the Contact XML file. The copy supports HTML formatting so you can change font size, colour and decoration and add hyper links. <br><br><img src="content/feature10.jpg"><br><font color="#FFFFFF" size="15"><b>MP3 Playlist Component</b></font><br>With this component you can add as many tracks as you wish by saving the MP3's to a specific folder and defining the track titles in the playlist XML file. This player also supports audio streaming and automatically plays through the playlist.<br><br><br>]]></item>
</content>